michelfortin.com 2004-06-14

# The Success Doctor™'s Privacy Policy

| 

|  |  

|   
---  
  
  | **Services**  
---  

**Questions?**  

**Resources**  

**About Me**  

"I just wanted to thank you, Michel, for writing such a fantastic website sales letter for us! So far, our income has quadrupled. In fact, we've made in one week what we would usually make in an entire month! Michel, you have a way with words -- and I'll certainly be calling upon you in the future to help us maximize our other projects. So far the second web salesletter you did is pulling at around 10%! Thank you for a great job! In fact, I really don't know what we'd do without you... So, please, don't go getting hit by a bus or anything! Thank you for everything!"  
**Tameka Sowder, Affiliate Mastery**

"What most people sometimes miss is that, whatever fees are paid to a copy writer of Michel's stature, it's indeed an investment. The boost in conversion rate and sales from Michel's work pays for the one time, initial cost, over and over again. Michel's work is defnitely tops."   
**Bob Silber, Internet Marketing Law Products**

"I've recommended Michel to my clients when they asked me for advice. My clients are usually very good friends, too, so that'll tell you what I think of his abilities and professionalism."  
**Paul Myers, TalkBiz.com**

"Michel, as to the email advertorial you wrote for me, it is _**OUTSTANDING**_ , my friend! It is very smooth, it sets up a good case and it piles the values on! And it even made 'me' want to buy it! I will use it as is." _  
_**Dr. Sheldon Nix _,_ The Successful Practice Institute**

"Michel Fortin is the King of Copywriting on the web. Check out his site. And while you're there, you'll also want to subscribe to his free newsletter as it's loaded with excellent content to help you become a better copywriter. He's the Man!"  
**Merle Stinett, Ezine Ad Auction**

"I hear _**NOTHING**_ but great things about you. (...) Your work is so darn good. I thought you might like to see this testimonial that one of my clients (I referred to you) sent me. Thanks for helping him!"  
**Ken McCarthy, Amacord.com (Dan Kennedy's Internet 'Guru')**

**Click for more...**  
  
### **The Success Doctor™'s Privacy Policy**

****

****At _SuccessDoctor.com_ , your privacy is assured. If you join the newsletter on this site, you will be kept posted on any developments that might benefit you (e.g., updates, announcements and special offers). However, note:

  * This site does not use "cookies" except for a single, nonidentifying one. It identifies you as a returning user but does not reveal any personal information about you. It's only a generic cookie used for the express purpose of limiting the number of times a popup appears. This is done strictly for the convenience of users and not used for any other purpose. Any cookie or pop-up window blocking (or removal) program will not interfere with the navigation or enjoyment of this site.  
 
  * This site does not gather personal information about you without your knowledge. Standard web server log files are kept for the sole purpose of administering this site. They include user statistics, IP addresses (to identify geographic locations only), user behavior (such as files requested), referrer URLs, time spent on each page, browser tags, OS tags, download quantities and screen resolutions.  
 
  * My mailing lists are and will remain completely confidential. They are not (and will never be) sold to, rented to or shared with anyone. Upon request, you will be promptly removed from my databases without any questions. (Please see below for easy removal instructions.) Although highly unlikely, a confirmation request will be emailed to you before any changes happen, if ever. I respect your trust.  
 
  * And this website contains numerous links to other sites on the web. This site is not responsible for or has no control over the respective privacy practices of such sites. Your judgment is encouraged.

If you received unsolicited commercial information about this website or its offerings from an unknown third party (i.e., "spam"), report the abuse to me immediately using this confidential form. Appropriate action will be taken.

Also, not that this site uses several third parties to handle certain business services. Great care was taken in their selection. But if you have received unsolicited email as a result of using these services, please do not hesitate to report it immediately as well. They will be discontinued immediately.

#### **To Opt-out or Modify**

Users are provided with the opportunity to easily opt-out of receiving future communications from Michel Fortin, modify information they've provided, or remove them from Mike's databases. You may do so in the following ways:

  * **Online:** Directly through **the mailing list** itself.
  * **Email:[removeme@successdoctor.com](mailto:removeme@successdoctor.com?subject=Remove%20Me%20Please "Email to remove your address from the mailing list!") **(use the correct email address at which you receive your mailings for proper removal)
  * **Mail:** 1561 Demeter Street, Ottawa, Ontario K4A-4Y9 (Canada)
  * **Telephone or facsimile:** 613-834-6918

#### Children's Privacy

I do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. If I learn at any time that I have personal information on a child under the age of 13, I will delete that information from my systems and databases.

_The Success Doctor_ encourages parents to go online with their kids. Here are a few tips to help make a child's online experience safer (you can also [check out the FTC's website](http://www.ftc.gov/bcp/conline/edcams/kidzprivacy/index.html) for more tips on protecting children's privacy online):

* Teach kids never to give personal information, unless supervised by a parent or adult guardian (includes name, address, phone, school, etc).
* Know the sites your kids are visiting and which sites are appropriate.
* Look for website privacy policies (and read them) of those visited by your child so you know how your child's information is treated.

#### **Questions?**

If you have any questions, comments or concerns about this privacy pledge or about the practices of this website, do not hesitate to **contact me** at any time, in complete confidence, or call me directly at (613) 834-6918.

> **The Privacy Partnership Pledge:** _"The Internet is an online community that allows unparalleled access to information. And community is built on trust and inherent in that trust is your right to privacy. As such, you deserve to choose what information you want to share, and to know what will happen to that information once you have shared it. This is your right."_

This site adheres to this pledge by being a member of TRUSTe's online _Privacy Partnership_. Join me in supporting the _**[Privacy Partnership](http://www.truste.org/partners)**_. Finally, for more on privacy policies and guidelines, visit the _**[Online Privacy Alliance](http://www.privacyalliance.org/)**_.

##### **If You Like What You Read...**

### Subscribe to My Free Email Newsletter!

##### Bonus! Subscribe to my _FREE_ monthly ezine, "The Profit Pill," and you'll instantly get a special gift with your subscription...

#### **A _FREE_ eBook ($19.95 Value)!**

Join right now, and receive copywriting tips and tools delivered to your email inbox each month. An email will be sent to you asking you to confirm your subscription.

Once you confirm your subscription, I'll send you your free gift — a copy of my book, _The 10 Commandments of Power Positioning_ , attached to your confirmation email (I'll include a link to read it online will be included, too.)
